	Good day, I am Ekaterina, and I am delighted to be here today. I appreciate the opportunity to discuss my qualifications for the [Position / Job Title] role.
	I have been a Java Developer [or studied Java] for a number of years [Company / University name] now and since I first started work, I have constantly sought to improve and develop my skills. I am proficient with programming languages [Skillset; Languages: Java, JavaScrip... ; Projects]; I have an inquisitive nature that ensures I analyze my work and the problems I encounter in detail [Example]; I am quick to learn new concepts and can apply them to a variety of situations [Example].  I am a strong team worker who can collaborate with and work alongside others to complete challenging projects and also resolve complex issues and problems [Example].
	I am highly self-motivated, technically astute and you can rely on me to get up to speed quickly in the role whilst being a cooperative, responsive and adaptable member of your team.  